final List<Map<String, dynamic>> providers = [
  {
    'name': 'Alex Scriba',
    'address': '7 Nathan Road, Yau Ma Tei',
    'questions': [
      {
        'question': 'Are you open at nights?',
        'answer': 'No we are only open during normal working hours.',
      }
    ],
    'providerType': 0,
    'consultationType': 1,
    'location': 1,
    'gender': 0,
    'ageGroup': 1,
    'treatments': 2,
    'values': [0, 2, 1, 7]
  },
  {
    'name': 'Matthew Betty',
    'address': '21 Nathan Road, Yau Ma Tei',
    'questions': [
      {
        'question': 'Do you have experience with anxiety?',
        'answer': 'Yes I work with anxiety patients all the time.',
      }
    ],
    'providerType': 1,
    'consultationType': 2,
    'location': 3,
    'gender': 1,
    'ageGroup': 2,
    'treatments': 0,
    'values': [2, 5, 0, 1]
  },
  {
    'name': 'Matthew Chamberlin',
    'address': '21 Kowloon Road, Yau Ma Tei',
    'questions': [
      {
        'question': 'Do you help youths?',
        'answer': 'I am a youth myself.',
      }
    ],
    'providerType': 0,
    'consultationType': 0,
    'location': 0,
    'gender': 0,
    'ageGroup': 0,
    'treatments': 0,
    'values': [0, 1, 2, 3]
  },
  {
    'name': 'Mike Kursewski',
    'address': '21 Boet Road, Mong Kok',
    'questions': [
      {
        'question': 'Is it possible to have a test session online?',
        'answer':
            'Yes, the test session will be 15 minutes online at half price.',
      }
    ],
    'providerType': 1,
    'consultationType': 1,
    'location': 1,
    'gender': 1,
    'ageGroup': 1,
    'treatments': 1,
    'values': [1, 3, 5, 4]
  },
  {
    'name': 'Milind Sharma',
    'address': '21 Mong Kok Road, Mong Kok',
    'questions': [
      {
        'question': 'Are you able to treat to prescribe drugs?',
        'answer': 'No, I am a trained psychologist, not a psychiatrist.',
      }
    ],
    'providerType': 0,
    'consultationType': 3,
    'location': 1,
    'gender': 2,
    'ageGroup': 0,
    'treatments': 1,
    'values': [3, 6, 1, 2]
  },
  {
    'name': 'Leo Fridjeoff',
    'address': '22 Cornwall Road, Yau Ma Tei',
    'questions': [
      {
        'question': 'Can I organize regular sessions?',
        'answer': 'You can set recurring sessions in the apps booking system.',
      }
    ],
    'providerType': 1,
    'consultationType': 1,
    'location': 2,
    'gender': 0,
    'ageGroup': 1,
    'treatments': 1,
    'values': [3, 4, 2, 3]
  },
  {
    'name': 'Gimmie Zimmerwoman',
    'address': '26 Lurgan Road, Yau Ma Tei',
    'questions': [
      {
        'question': 'Can I book appointments during the weekend?',
        'answer':
            'Yes, my hours are 9-6 during the week and 9-12 on the weekend',
      }
    ],
    'providerType': 2,
    'consultationType': 1,
    'location': 2,
    'gender': 0,
    'ageGroup': 1,
    'treatments': 2,
    'values': [5, 1, 4, 2]
  },
  {
    'name': 'Bharadwaj Sata Rajosh',
    'address': '21 Nathan Road, Yau Ma Tei',
    'questions': [
      {
        'question': 'Can you treat me with CBT?',
        'answer':
            'Unfortunately this is not my area of expertise, please refer to another professional',
      }
    ],
    'providerType': 2,
    'consultationType': 1,
    'location': 0,
    'gender': 2,
    'ageGroup': 0,
    'treatments': 1,
    'values': [5, 4, 3, 2]
  },
  {
    'name': 'Frederick Knowles',
    'address': '2 Dund Street, Central',
    'questions': [
      {
        'question': 'How long will appointments with you be?',
        'answer':
            'Normally 30 minutes, but this can change depending on the patient.',
      }
    ],
    'providerType': 0,
    'consultationType': 1,
    'location': 0,
    'gender': 2,
    'ageGroup': 2,
    'treatments': 2,
    'values': [4, 3, 2, 1]
  },
  {
    'name': 'Mike Chambers',
    'address': '21 Kimberly Street, Shatin',
    'questions': [
      {
        'question':
            'Does your confidentiality agreement extend to my family members?',
        'answer':
            'Yes, everything said in my office will never be repeated elsewhere.',
      }
    ],
    'providerType': 2,
    'consultationType': 2,
    'location': 2,
    'gender': 2,
    'ageGroup': 2,
    'treatments': 2,
    'values': [1, 2, 4, 3]
  },
];
